gstindia.com 2018-10-20

# Disclaimer – Privacy Policy – Terms of use. – GST India-Goods and Services Tax in India

#### Disclaimer

 _ **Welcome to GSTINDIA.com.**_

> Our visitors are our lifeline.

We value our Site Visitors  and respect your right to privacy. We do not engage in SPAM or JUNK, nor do we share the personal contact information of our stores, visitors, or their friends, relatives, and associates with third parties. The following information provides more detail about our Privacy Policy.

**No Rendering of Advice**

_**GSTINDIA.com**_  do not provide tax, legal or accounting advice. This material has been prepared for informational purposes only, and is not intended to provide, and should not be relied on for, tax, legal or accounting advice. You should consult your own tax, legal and accounting advisers before engaging in any transaction.

**Accuracy of Information**

While we make reasonable efforts to furnish accurate and up-to-date information, we do not warrant that any information contained in or made available through this website is accurate, complete, reliable, current or error-free. We assume no responsibility for any errors or omissions in the content of this website or such other materials or communications.

**Disclaimer of Warranties and Limitations of Liability**

This website is provided on an “as is” and “as available” basis. Use of this website is at your own risk. We and our affiliates disclaim all warranties. Neither we nor our affiliates shall be liable for any damages of any kind due to the use of this website.

**Links to Third Party Websites**

For your convenience, this website may contain hyperlinks to websites and servers maintained by third parties. We not control, evaluate, endorse or guarantee content found in those sites. We do not assume any responsibility for the actions, products, services and content of these sites or the parties that operate them. Your use of such sites I entirely at your own risk.

#### Privacy Policy

This **Privacy Policy** governs the manner in which _**GSTINDIA.com**_  collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the https://www.gstindia.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by GST India.

1\. PERSONAL IDENTIFICATION INFORMATION

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

2\. NON-PERSONAL IDENTIFICATION INFORMATION

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers’ utilized and other similar information.

3\. WEB BROWSER COOKIES

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

4\. HOW WE USE COLLECTED INFORMATION

We may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

(a) To improve visitor service – Information you provide helps us respond to your visitor service requests and support needs more efficiently.

(b) To personalize user experience – We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.

(c) To improve our Site – We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.

(d) To process payments – We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.

(e) To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature – To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.

(f) To send periodic emails – We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

5\. HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. Our Site is also in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users.

6\. SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

7\. GOOGLE ADSENSE

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at [http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/)

8. COMPLIANCE WITH CHILDREN’S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. _**GSTINDIA.com**_  further does not promote, condone or endorse the dissemination of information, or sale of products and services to minors when prohibited by law; including the dissemination or sale of pornographic materials to minors; and the sale of firearms, tobacco and alcohol to minors.

9.CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

_**GSTINDIA.com**_ have the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

#### Terms of use

If you continue to browse and use this website, you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions of use, which together with our Privacy Statement and Copyright & Trademark Infringement govern GST India’s relationship with you.

The use of this website is subject to the following terms and conditions of use:

  * The content of the pages of this website is for your general information and use only. It is subject to change without notice.
  * We do not provide legal, professional or any other advice and you should always seek independent advice before acting on any information on the website.
  * Your use of any information or materials on this website is entirely at your own risk, for which we shall not be liable. It shall be your own responsibility to ensure that any services or information available through this website meet your specific requirements.
  * We take all care in ensuring that all information we provide in the website is accurate but we are not responsible for any loss suffered by you as a consequence of any that action you take or omit to take on the basis of any of the information we provide.
  * We are not be liable for any loss suffered by you through the use of the website howsoever caused, including loss caused through but not limited to our negligence, breach of contract, copyright infringement, breach of other intellectual property rights or defamation.
  * We are not liable for content published on the website by users of the website. If any such content appears to be inappropriate to us, we reserve the right to take down such content.
  * You shall not publish or cause to be published any unlawful, defamatory, obscene, offensive, harmful or otherwise objectionable content on the website.
  * We shall not sell, market, trade, or transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. We may release your information when the release is required to comply with the law, enforce our policies, protect our or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
  * This website also contains material which is owned by us. This material includes, but is not limited to, the design, layout, look, appearance and graphics. Reproduction is prohibited other than in accordance with the copyright notice, which forms part of these terms and conditions.
  * You must refrain from using the website in any way that causes damage to the website or in any unlawful, harmful or fraudulent manner. Any such use of this website may give rise to a claim for damages and/or be a criminal offence.
  * You must respect the use of the website by other users and not interfere with their legitimate use of the website and our services.
  * You hereby agree not to post material including spamming which is deliberately intended to upset other users.
  * From time to time this website may also include links to other websites. These links are provided for your convenience to provide further information. They do not signify that we endorse the website(s). These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies and, therefore, we owe no responsibility for the content of the linked website(s).
  * When registering on our site, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, location. We may also collect information about your computer, your IP address and your use of this website. Any of such information which we collect from you may be used to improve our website or to administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * We will take all reasonable and necessary care to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access our website.
  * GST India does not subscribe to the views of authors and does not in any way confirm or deny the opinion expressed therein, and shall not be treated as the opinion of GST India.
  * When you join GST India, the details you enter on the registration form will be used by us to provide you with our premium services. While registering, you agree to provide your real first name, last name, e-mail address and truthful personal information.
  * You agree to keep your username and password safe from use by third parties and not share your registration details with anyone else. You will be liable to indemnify us against any unauthorised use of your username and password, howsoever caused.
  * We reserve the right to delete, disable and/or restrict your account.
  * Although we will do our best to provide constant, uninterrupted access to the website, we do not guarantee this nor do we accept any responsibility or liability for any interruption or delay.
  * _Copyright Notice_ **.** Except as otherwise noted on this Website, the contents of this Website are copyrighted © 2016 by GST India. All rights are reserved. No part of the information on this Website, including text, graphics and html code, may be reproduced or transmitted in any form by any means, without the express written consent of GST India. Copyrights mentioned by third parties/links are protected under their Laws and we do not have copyright on their mentioned contents.
  * Your use of this website and any dispute arising out of such use of the website is subject to the laws of India and to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts in Mumbai.
